Jake Lipson

jlips@bu.edu www.jakelipson.com GitHub: jlips24 207 E 21st Street New York, New York 10010 (845) 825-9329

Objective

Adaptable professional with 4+ years of proven experience in application development, web design, and backend programming. Eager to leverage my skills to exceed expectations in a team based environment filling the Software Engineer role at your company.

EDUCATION

Boston UniversityBachelor of Arts, Computer Science

Boston, MA January 2019

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming/Markup Languages: Java, Python, Docker, Django, Flask, Pandas, AWS, GCS, C++, HTML, CSS. SQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Spotify New York, NY

Software Engineer

April 2021 - December 2023

- Responsible for the advertiser accounts flow of Spotify's advertising platform.
- Designed and built the Spotify ad accounts API 2.0 using OpenAPI.
- Developed features in a many micro services such as the ad accounts backend, business entity management, promo codes, and more.
- Worked with management to continually improve our SCRUM and documentation practices.

Noodle Partners New York, NY

Software Engineer

January 2020 - April 2021

- Built, maintained and implemented a complex Python ETL library.
- Helped build web applications using Diango and Flask.
- Supported the development of a custom in-house built Salesforce package.
- Made business critical decisions ranging from software design to implementation of an AGILE workflow.

Noodle Pros New York, NY

Software Engineer Contractor

January 2020 - June 2020

- Designed and led data migration to new and improved systems.
- Continued to manage day to day database operations company-wide.
- Dedicated time outside of normal work hours to ensure projects were completed.

Noodle Management Services

New York, NY

Software Engineer Intern

July 2019 - January 2020

- Managed day to day database operations company-wide.
- Implemented automated workflows using Python to increase company efficiency.
- Migrated large datasets from Hubspot to Salesforce.

Apple Store Boylston Street

Boston, MA

Specialist

September 2017 - March 2018

- Identified customers' requirements and mapped to compatible solutions.
- Informed customers about new hardware and software.
- Assisted customers in the setup of their new devices.